Guide to the Big Band Arrangements Collection, 1990-2017 SC.2017.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Nine-Man Arrangements, II.
  - You and Me Against the World (Box 36, Folder 556)
  - You Are My Lucky Star, Vocal (D) (Box 37, Folder 679)
  - You Belong to Me, Vocal (F or Bb) (Box 38, Folder 786)
  - You Belong to Me, Vocal (Bb) (Box 39, Folder 862)
  - You Go to My Head (Box 35, Folder 492)
  - You Made Me Love You (Harry James) (Box 36, Folder 633)
  - You Make Me Feel So Young (Box 34, Folder 350)
  - You Took Advantage of Me, Vocal (G) (Box 37, Folder 691)
  - You Turned the Tables on Me (Box 38, Folder 751)
  - You'll Never Find Another Love Like Mine (Louis Rawls), Vocal (Bb) (Box 33, Folder 325)
  - You're Driving Me Crazy (Billy May) (Box 31, Folder 75)
  - You're Nobody 'Till Somebody Loves You, Vocals (Db, Eb, F) (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - You're Wonderful (Box 33, Folder 273)
  - Yours (Box 33, Folder 215)
- Tenor Arrangements, III.
  - A Nightingale Sang in Berkley Square, Vocal (Eb) (Box 44, Folder 616)
  - A Taste of Honey (Box 41, Folder 188)
  - Adam's Apple (Box 41, Folder 226)
  - Address Unknown (Box 41, Folder 238)
  - After the Lovin' (Box 42, Folder 278)
  - After the Lovin', Vocal (A) (Box 44, Folder 612)
  - Ain't Misbehavin' (Box 41, Folder 245)
  - Ain't She Sweet (Box 43, Folder 362)
  - Alamo (Box 42, Folder 314a)
  - Alfie (Box 41, Folder 182)
  - Alice's Restaurant (Box 41, Folder 248)
  - Alley Cat (Box 41, Folder 209)
  - Angry (Box 42, Folder 296)
  - Another Somebody Wrong Song (Box 40, Folder 130)
  - Armed Forces Marches (Box 44, Folder 506)
  - Aquarius (Box 41, Folder 249)
  - Artist's Life Waltz (Box 43, Folder 410)
  - At Last (Box 40, Folder 118)
  - Avalon (Box 43, Folder 408)
  - Bad Bad Leroy Brown (Box 43, Folder 421)
  - Beer Barrel Polka (Box 43, Folder 445)
  - Bei Mir Bist Du Schon (Box 43, Folder 376)
  - Begin the Beguine (Box 43, Folder 430)
  - Beginning to See the Light, Vocal (A) (Box 44, Folder 606)
  - Besame Mucho (Box 43, Folder 404)
  - Bewitched (Box 40, Folder 116)
  - Beyond the Reef (Box 41, Folder 187)
  - Big Band Themes (Box 43, Folder 455)
  - Bill Haley Medley (Box 44, Folder 620)
  - Birdland (Box 41, Folder 189)
  - Birdland (Box 42, Folder 315)
  - Blue Bayou (Box 44, Folder 447)
  - Blue Heaven (Box 41, Folder 230)
  - Blue Medley (Box 41, Folder 228)
  - Blue Tango (Box 43, Folder 405)
  - Blue Skies (Box 41, Folder 200)
  - Blues in the Closet (Box 41, Folder 231)
  - Boogie Oogie Oogie (Box 41, Folder 112a)
  - Boogie Woogie (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Born to Lose (Box 43, Folder 400a)
  - Brazil (Box 43, Folder 363)
  - Brown Eyes Blue (Box 40, Folder 124)
  - Bunny Hop (Box 40, Folder 127)
  - But Beautiful (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - C Jam Blues (Box 41, Folder 202)
  - Cab Driver (Box 43, Folder 364)
  - Can We Talk This Over (Box 43, Folder 396)
  - Cabaret (Box 40, Folder 136)
  - Canadian Sunset (Box 40, Folder 168a)
  - Canadian Sunset (Box 42, Folder 287)
  - Candy Man (Box 40, Folder 137)
  - Cecelia (Box 42, Folder 267)
  - Chanson D'Amour (Box 42, Folder 284)
  - Charmaine (Box 40, Folder 133)
  - Cha Cha Flemenco (Box 42, Folder 311)
  - Charleston (Box 42, Folder 347)
  - Chattanooga Choo Choo (Box 41, Folder 235)
  - Cheek to Cheek (Box 42, Folder 293)
  - Cherry Pickers' Polka (Box 43, Folder 380)
  - Cherry Pink (Box 43, Folder 401)
  - Cherry Pink and Apple Blossom White (Box 41, Folder 197)
  - Chicago (Box 42, Folder 300)
  - Christopher Columbus (Box 41, Folder 234)
  - Close to You (Box 40, Folder 125)
  - Colonel Bogey Merengue (Box 42, Folder 328)
  - Copacabana (Box 42, Folder 322)
  - Cuddle Up a Little Closer (Box 43, Folder 414)
  - Cupid (Box 40, Folder 171)
  - Dancing With Tears in My Eyes (Box 43, Folder 397)
  - Danke Schoen (Box 41, Folder 178)
  - Darn that Dream (Box 43, Folder 456)
  - Deep Purple (Box 40, Folder 143)
  - Deep Purple (Box 42, Folder 328a)
  - Do That to Me One More Time (Box 41, Folder 241)
  - Does Your Heart Beat for Me (Box 40, Folder 161)
  - Dolly (Box 41, Folder 242)
  - Don't Be That Way (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Don't Blame Me, Vocal (C) (Box 44, Folder 602)
  - Don't Go to Strangers (Box 40, Folder 126)
  - Don't Take Your Love Away from Me (Box 42, Folder 324)
  - Don't Take Your Love Away from Me, Vocal (C) (Box 44, Folder 601)
  - Down Yonder in New Orleans (Box 42, Folder 297)
  - Dream (Box 42, Folder 301)
  - Driving Me Crazy (Box 41, Folder 183)
  - Early Autumn (Box 43, Folder 454)
  - Easy Street (Box 43, Folder 390b)
  - Easy to Love (Box 41, Folder 258)
  - End of a Rainbow (Box 41, Folder 256)
  - Even Now (Box 42, Folder 277)
  - Fairy Bell Polka (Box 43, Folder 428)
  - Feelings (Box 42, Folder 309)
  - Feelings, Vocal (Eb) (Box 44, Folder 608)
  - Fiesta (Box 43, Folder 416)
  - Fine and Dandy (Box 42, Folder 345)
  - Five Foot Two (Box 44, Folder 450)
  - Flamingo (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Fly Me to the Moon (Box 40, Folder 162)
  - For All We Know (Box 41, Folder 237)
  - For the Good Times (Box 41, Folder 179)
  - For Once in My Life (Box 41, Folder 195)
  - Frenesi (Box 42, Folder 337a)
  - Games People Play (Box 41, Folder 196)
  - Georgy Girl (Box 41, Folder 210)
  - Getting Sentimental (Box 40, Folder 170)
  - Gotta Date With an Angel (Box 42, Folder 351)
  - Greig (Box 43, Folder 360)
  - Guantanamera (Box 40, Folder 157)
  - Harbor Lights (Box 42, Folder 334)
  - Harlem Nocturne (Box 40, Folder 115)
  - Hava Nagila (Box 40, Folder 139)
  - Hawaiian Isle Medley (Box 42, Folder 269)
  - Heart and Soul (Box 43, Folder 409)
  - Hindustan (Box 41, Folder 244)
  - Home (Box 42, Folder 354)
  - Honky Tonk (Box 41, Folder 222)
  - How Deep is Your Love (Box 43, Folder 391)
  - How Insensitive (Box 42, Folder 335a)
  - I Can Dream, Can't I? (Box 43, Folder 425)
  - I Do, I Do, I Do (Box 40, Folder 164)
  - I Don't Want to Walk Without You, Vocal (Ab) (Box 44, Folder 609)
  - I Get a Kick Out of You, Vocal (Ab) (Box 44, Folder 603)
  - I Guess I'll Have to Change My Plans (Box 43, Folder 394)
  - I Love Paris (Box 43, Folder 433)
  - I May Be Wrong (Box 41, Folder 213)
  - I Talk to the Trees (Box 41, Folder 180)
  - I'll Remember April (Box 41, Folder 261)
  - I'll String Along with You (Box 40, Folder 108)
  - I've Got You Under My Skin (Box 43, Folder 361)
  - If Ever I Would Leave You (Box 40, Folder 131)
  - If I Loved You (Box 43, Folder 370)
  - If I Sing You a Love Song (Box 40, Folder 156)
  - Impossible (Box 44, Folder 651)
  - Impossible Dream (Box 40, Folder 150)
  - In the Arms of Love (Box 40, Folder 167)
  - In the Mood (Box 41, Folder 233)
  - Ipanema (Box 43, Folder 444)
  - Isle of Capri (Box 41, Folder 265)
  - Isle of Capri (Box 42, Folder 337)
  - It Isn't Fair (Box 40, Folder 149)
  - It Must Be Him (Box 40, Folder 168)
  - It's Impossible (Box 40, Folder 109)
  - Italian Medley (Box 40, Folder 128)
  - Jalousie (Box 43, Folder 411)
  - Jerome Kern Medley (Box 42, Folder 308)
  - Jersey Bounce (Box 43, Folder 457)
  - Johnson Rag (Box 41, Folder 207)
  - Josephine (Box 43, Folder 374)
  - Jumpin' at the Woodside (Box 42, Folder 273)
  - June in January (Box 43, Folder 424)
  - Kansas City (Box 40, Folder 63)
  - Kansas City (Box 43, Folder 453)
  - Killer Joe (Box 43, Folder 443)
  - Knock Three Times (Box 42, Folder 330)
  - La Bamba (Box 42, Folder 339a)
  - La Rosita (Box 40, Folder 159)
  - Laura (Box 40, Folder 123)
  - Lazy River (Box 43, Folder 359)
  - Let It Snow (Box 42, Folder 292)
  - Let's Dance (Box 44, Folder 623)
  - Little Brown Jug (Box 41, Folder 236)
  - Little Girl (Box 42, Folder 346)
  - Lollipops and Roses (Box 40, Folder 155)
  - Lonely Bull (Box 41, Folder 177)
  - Love (Box 41, Folder 217)
  - Love is Just Around the Corner (Box 42, Folder 339)
  - Love is Just Around the Corner (Box 43, Folder 419)
  - Love Letters (Box 40, Folder 151)
  - Love Story (Box 43, Folder 390)
  - Love to Keep Me Warm (Box 41, Folder 203)
  - Love to Keep Me Warm (Box 42, Folder 326)
  - Ma, He's Making Eyes at Me (Box 42, Folder 299)
  - Mack the Knife (Box 41, Folder 253)
  - Mambo No. 5 (Box 41, Folder 212)
  - Margie (Box 42, Folder 353)
  - Marie (Box 41, Folder 218)
  - Marie Elena (Box 43, Folder 426)
  - Marie Elena, Vocal (Bb) (Box 44, Folder 600)
  - Martha (Box 43, Folder 356)
  - Mathilda (Box 43, Folder 386a)
  - Medley-100 (Box 41, Folder 100)
  - Medley-100 (a) Prisoner (Box 40, Folder 100)
  - Medley-100 (b) Penthouse (Box 40, Folder 100)
  - Medley-100 (c) What a Difference a Day Makes (Box 40, Folder 100)
  - Medley-101 (Box 40, Folder 101)
  - Medley-101 (a) Gigi (Box 40, Folder 101)
  - Medley-101 (b) Polka Dots (Box 40, Folder 101)
  - Medley-102 (Box 40, Folder 102)
  - Medley-102 (a) Scotch & Soda (Box 40, Folder 102)
  - Medley-102 (b) All My Tomorrows (Box 40, Folder 102)
  - Medley-103 (Box 40, Folder 103)
  - Medley-103 (a) Trust in Me (Box 40, Folder 103)
  - Medley-103 (b) My Devotion (Box 40, Folder 103)
  - Medley-103 (c) Our Love is Here to Stay (Box 40, Folder 103)
  - Medley-104 (Box 40, Folder 104)
  - Medley-104 (a) Careless (Box 40, Folder 104)
  - Medley-104 (b) Lilacs (Box 40, Folder 104)
  - Medley-105 (Box 40, Folder 104)
  - Medley-105 (a) Sweet Eloise (Box 40, Folder 105)
  - Medley-105 (b) Linda (Box 40, Folder 105)
  - Medley-106 (Box 40, Folder 106)
  - Medley-106 (a) My Prayer (Box 40, Folder 106)
  - Medley-106 (b) Reverie (Box 40, Folder 106)
  - Medley-110 (Box 40, Folder 110)
  - Medley-110 (a) For All We Know (Box 40, Folder 110)
  - Medley-110 (b) June in January (Box 40, Folder 110)
  - Medley-110 (c) Smiles (Box 40, Folder 110)
  - Medley-120 (Box 40, Folder 120)
  - Medley-120 (a) Hands Across the Table (Box 40, Folder 120)
  - Medley-120 (b) Baby's Prayer (Box 40, Folder 120)
  - Medley-120 (c) Home (Box 40, Folder 120)
  - Medley-121 (Box 40, Folder 121)
  - Medley-121 (a) Red Sails (Box 40, Folder 121)
  - Medley-121 (b) Moon Over Miami (Box 40, Folder 121)
  - Medley-121 (c) Moonlight Bay (Box 40, Folder 121)
  - Medley-132 (Box 40, Folder 132)
  - Medley-132 (a) Harvest Moon (Box 40, Folder 132)
  - Medley-132 (b) Sleepy Time Gal (Box 40, Folder 132)
  - Medley-132 (c) Swinging Down the Lane (Box 40, Folder 132)
  - Medley-140 (Box 40, Folder 140)
  - Medley-140 (a) A Fine Romance (Box 40, Folder 140)
  - Medley-140 (b) How Many Hearts (Box 40, Folder 140)
  - Medley-140 (c) I Cried for You (Box 40, Folder 140)
  - Medley-174 (Box 40, Folder 174)
  - Medley-174 (a) Cecilia Johnson Rag (Box 40, Folder 174)
  - Medley-174 (b) My Melancholy Baby (Box 40, Folder 174)
  - Medley-166 (Box 40, Folder 166)
  - Medley-166 (a) Arrivederci (Box 40, Folder 166)
  - Medley-166 (b) I Wish I Knew (Box 40, Folder 166)
  - Medley-166 (c) Paper Roses (Box 40, Folder 166)
  - Medley-185 (Box 41, Folder 185)
  - Medley-185 (a) Miss You (Box 41, Folder 185)
  - Medley-185 (b) As Time Goes By (Box 41, Folder 185)
  - Medley-240 (Box 41, Folder 240)
  - Medley-240 (a) For You (Box 41, Folder 240)
  - Medley-240 (b) Shanty Town (Box 41, Folder 240)
  - Medley-240 (c) Oh How I Miss You Tonight (Box 41, Folder 240)
  - Medley-246 (Box 41, Folder 246)
  - Medley-246 (a) St. Louis Blues (Box 41, Folder 246)
  - Medley-246 (b) Music Goes 'Round and Around (Box 41, Folder 246)
  - Medley-246 (c) Way Down Yonder in New Orleans (Box 41, Folder 246)
  - Medley-254 (Richard Rodgers) (Box 41, Folder 254)
  - Medley-254 (a) Blue Moon (Box 41, Folder 254)
  - Medley-254 (b) Manhattan (Box 41, Folder 254)
  - Medley-254 (c) You Are Too Beautiful (Box 41, Folder 254)
  - Medley-255 (Box 41, Folder 255)
  - Medley-255 (a) Careless (Box 41, Folder 255)
  - Medley-255 (b) Sweet and Lovely (Box 41, Folder 255)
  - Medley-255 (c) Falling in Love
  - Medley-255 (d) Dearly Beloved (Box 41, Folder 255)
  - Medley-255 (d) Tree in a Meadow (Box 41, Folder 255)
  - Medley-257 (Box 41, Folder 257)
  - Medley-257 (a) Linda (Box 41, Folder 257)
  - Medley-257 (b) Rosale (Box 41, Folder 257)
  - Medley-257 (c) Louise (Box 41, Folder 257)
  - Medley-262 (Box 41, Folder 262)
  - Medley-262 (a) When You're Smiling (Box 41, Folder 262)
  - Medley-262 (b) When My Baby Smiles at Me (Box 41, Folder 262)
  - Medley-262 (c) Smiles (Box 41, Folder 262)
  - Medley-263 (Box 41, Folder 263)
  - Medley-263 (a) Cuddle Up a Little Closer (Box 41, Folder 263)
  - Medley-263 (b) The Gang That Sang Heart of My Heart (Box 41, Folder 263)
  - Medley-263 (c) Wedding Bells Are Breaking Up (Box 41, Folder 263)
  - Medley-264 (Box 41, Folder 264)
  - Medley-264 (a) Beyond the Reef (Box 41, Folder 264)
  - Medley-264 (b) Bali Hai (Box 41, Folder 264)
  - Medley-264 (c) Wedding Song (Box 41, Folder 264)
  - Medley-266 (Box 42, Folder 266)
  - Medley-266 (a) Baubles, Bangles, and Beads (Box 42, Folder 266)
  - Medley-266 (c) Blue Skies (Box 42, Folder 266)
  - Medley-266 (b) Take the A Train (Box 42, Folder 266)
  - Medley-268 (Box 42, Folder 268)
  - Medley-268 (a) 42nd Street (Box 42, Folder 268)
  - Medley-268 (b) Anything Goes (Box 42, Folder 268)
  - Medley-268 (c) Everything I've Got (Box 42, Folder 268)
  - Medley-268 (d) Sophomore Swing (Box 42, Folder 268)
  - Medley-271 (Box 42, Folder 271)
  - Medley-271 (a) My Devotion (Box 42, Folder 271)
  - Medley-271 (b) Why Do I Love You (Box 42, Folder 271)
  - Medley-271 (c) My Heart Tells Me (Box 42, Folder 271)
  - Medley-272 (Box 42, Folder 272)
  - Medley-272 (a) Song of Old Hawaii (Box 42, Folder 272)
  - Medley-272 (b) Moon of Manakoora (Box 42, Folder 272)
  - Medley-272 (c) Blue Hawaii (Box 42, Folder 272)
  - Medley-274 (Box 42, Folder 274)
  - Medley-274 (a) Me and My Shadow (Box 42, Folder 274)
  - Medley-274 (b) Eighteenth Century (Box 42, Folder 274)
  - Medley-281 (Box 42, Folder 281)
  - Medley-281 (a) Chapel in the Moonlight (Box 42, Folder 281)
  - Medley-281 (b) Mission of St. Augustine (Box 42, Folder 281)
  - Medley-283 (Box 42, Folder 283)
  - Medley-283 (a) Huguette Waltz (Box 42, Folder 283)
  - Medley-283 (b) Someday (Box 42, Folder 283)
  - Medley-286 (Box 42, Folder 286)
  - Medley-286 (a) Al-Di-La (Box 42, Folder 286)
  - Medley-286 (b) Mala Femmina (Box 42, Folder 286)
  - Medley-290 (Box 42, Folder 290)
  - Medley-290 (a) Moonlight Becomes You (Box 42, Folder 290)
  - Medley-290 (b) Together (Box 42, Folder 290)
  - Medley-290 (c) I Married an Angel (Box 42, Folder 290)
  - Medley-291 (Box 42, Folder 291)
  - Medley-291 (a) Body and Soul (Box 42, Folder 291)
  - Medley-291 (b) The Nearness of You (Box 42, Folder 291)
  - Medley-291 (c) I Should Care (Box 42, Folder 291)
  - Medley-294 (Box 42, Folder 294)
  - Medley-294 (a) Frosty the Snowman (Box 42, Folder 294)
  - Medley-294 (b) Christmas Song (Box 42, Folder 294)
  - Medley-294 (c) Doing New Year's Eve (Box 42, Folder 294)
  - Medley-303 (Box 42, Folder 303)
  - Medley-303 (a) Whiffenpoof (Box 42, Folder 303)
  - Medley-303 (b) Jeanine (Box 42, Folder 303)
  - Medley-303 (c) Put Your Dreams Away (Box 42, Folder 303)
  - Medley-304 (Box 42, Folder 304)
  - Medley-304 (a) Whiffenpoof (Box 42, Folder 304)
  - Medley-304 (b) Aching Heart (Box 42, Folder 304)
  - Medley-304 (c) 'Till We Meet Again (Box 42, Folder 304)
  - Medley-306 (Box 42, Folder 306)
  - Medley-306 (a) Paris Skies (Box 42, Folder 306)
  - Medley-306 (b) Lose Your Love in Paris (Box 42, Folder 306)
  - Medley-306 (c) Lili (Box 42, Folder 306)
  - Medley-307 (Box 42, Folder 307)
  - Medley-307 (a) Anniversary Song (Box 42, Folder 307)
  - Medley-307 (b) All My Love (Box 42, Folder 307)
  - Medley-307 (c) Anniversary Waltz (Box 42, Folder 307)
  - Medley-316 (Box 42, Folder 316)
  - Medley-316 (a) Dancing on the Ceiling (Box 42, Folder 316)
  - Medley-316 (b) You and the Night and the Music (Box 42, Folder 316)
  - Medley-316 (c) September in the Rain (Box 42, Folder 316)
  - Medley-340 (Box 42, Folder 340)
  - Medley-340 (a) La Cumparsita (Box 42, Folder 340)
  - Medley-340 (b) Adios Muchachos (Box 42, Folder 340)
  - Medley-343 (Box 42, Folder 343)
  - Medley-343 (a) When Day is Done (Box 42, Folder 343)
  - Medley-343 (b) Long Ago and Far Away (Box 42, Folder 343)
  - Medley-343 (c) Say It With Music (Box 42, Folder 343)
  - Medley-350 (Box 42, Folder 350)
  - Medley-350 (a) Lonesome and Sorry (Box 42, Folder 350)
  - Medley-350 (b) Nobody's Baby (Box 42, Folder 350)
  - Medley-350 (c) I Ain't Got Nobody (Box 42, Folder 350)
  - Medley-367 (Box 43, Folder 367)
  - Medley-367 (a) Diane (Box 43, Folder 367)
  - Medley-367 (b) I'll See You Again (Box 43, Folder 367)
  - Medley-367 (c) Deep in My Heart (Box 43, Folder 367)
  - Medley-369 (Box 43, Folder 369)
  - Medley-369 (a) Indian Love Song (Box 43, Folder 369)
  - Medley-369 (b) Pale Moon (Box 43, Folder 369)
  - Medley-369 (c) Shores of Minnetonka (Box 43, Folder 369)
  - Medley-377 (Box 43, Folder 377)
  - Medley-377 (a) Last Time I Saw Paris (Box 43, Folder 377)
  - Medley-377 (b) April in Paris (Box 43, Folder 377)
  - Medley-379 (Box 43, Folder 379)
  - Medley-379 (a) I Could Be With You (Box 43, Folder 379)
  - Medley-379 (b) Delores (Box 43, Folder 379)
  - Medley-379 (c) Gimme a Little Kiss (Box 43, Folder 379)
  - Medley-381 (Box 43, Folder 381)
  - Medley-381 (a) Apple Blossom Time (Box 43, Folder 381)
  - Medley-381 (b) My Wild Irish Rose (Box 43, Folder 381)
  - Medley-381 (c) Memories (Box 43, Folder 381)
  - Medley-382 (Box 43, Folder 382)
  - Medley-382 (a) Melody in Bb (Box 43, Folder 382)
  - Medley-382 (b) Liebestraum (Box 43, Folder 382)
  - Medley-383 (Box 43, Folder 383)
  - Medley-383 (a) Brasilia (Box 43, Folder 383)
  - Medley-383 (b) So What's New (Box 43, Folder 383)
  - Medley-384 (Box 43, Folder 384)
  - Medley-384 (a) Small Hotel (Box 43, Folder 384)
  - Medley-384 (b) Pretty Girl (Box 43, Folder 384)
  - Medley-384 (b) Swinging Down the Lane (Box 43, Folder 384)
  - Medley-385 (Box 43, Folder 385)
  - Medley-385 (a) I'll Get By (Box 43, Folder 385)
  - Medley-385 (b) Blue Moon (Box 43, Folder 385)
  - Medley-385 (c) It Must Be True (Box 43, Folder 385)
  - Medley-386 (Box 43, Folder 386)
  - Medley-386 (a) Have You Ever Been Lonely (Box 43, Folder 386)
  - Medley-386 (b) Just a Gigolo (Box 43, Folder 386)
  - Medley-386 (c) Straighten Up and Fly Right (Box 43, Folder 386)
  - Medley-387 (Box 43, Folder 387)
  - Medley-387 (a) Godfather (Box 43, Folder 387)
  - Medley-387 (b) Summer of '42 (Box 43, Folder 387)
  - Medley-388 (Box 43, Folder 388)
  - Medley-388 (a) Blue Moon (Box 43, Folder 388)
  - Medley-388 (b) Autumn in New York (Box 43, Folder 388)
  - Medley-388 (c) Moonlight Serenade (Box 43, Folder 388)
  - Medley-389 (Box 43, Folder 389)
  - Medley-389 (a) Tur a Lur a Lura (Box 43, Folder 389)
  - Medley-389 (b) Irish Eyes (Box 43, Folder 389)
  - Medley-395 (Box 43, Folder 395)
  - Medley-395 (a) They Say It's Wonderful (Box 43, Folder 395)
  - Medley-395 (b) I Surrender Dear (Box 43, Folder 395)
  - Medley-395 (c) Embraceable You (Box 43, Folder 395)
  - Medley-399 (Box 43, Folder 399)
  - Medley-399 (a) Intermezzo (Box 43, Folder 399)
  - Medley-399 (b) I'm Always Chasin' (Box 43, Folder 399)
  - Medley-399 (c) Moonlight and Rose (Box 43, Folder 399)
  - Medley-400 (Box 43, Folder 400)
  - Medley-400 (a) Fools Rush In (Box 43, Folder 400)
  - Medley-400 (b) Elmer's Tune (Box 43, Folder 400)
  - Medley-400 (c) Moonlight Cocktail (Box 43, Folder 400)
  - Medley-413 (Box 43, Folder 413)
  - Medley-413 (a) Hasta Mañana (Box 43, Folder 413)
  - Medley-413 (b) Eichas Negras (Box 43, Folder 413)
  - Medley-413 (c) Taboo (Box 43, Folder 413)
  - Medley-422 (Box 43, Folder 422)
  - Medley-422 (a) Golden Earrings (Box 43, Folder 422)
  - Medley-422 (b) Play Fiddle Play (Box 43, Folder 422)
  - Medley-422 (c) Play Gypsy Dance (Box 43, Folder 422)
  - Medley-435 (Box 43, Folder 435)
  - Medley-435 (a) For Me and My Gal (Box 43, Folder 435)
  - Medley-435 (b) Top Hat (Box 43, Folder 435)
  - Medley-436 (Box 43, Folder 436)
  - Medley-436 (a) I Only Have Eyes for You (Box 43, Folder 436)
  - Medley-436 (b) Might as Well Be Spring (Box 43, Folder 436)
  - Medley-437 (Box 43, Folder 437)
  - Medley-437 (a) Exactly Like You (Box 43, Folder 437)
  - Medley-437 (b) At Sundown (Box 43, Folder 437)
  - Medley-438 (Jan Garber) (Box 43, Folder 438)
  - Medley-438 (a) Wake the Town and Tell the People (Box 43, Folder 438)
  - Medley-438 (b) South Sea Island Magic (Box 43, Folder 438)
  - Medley-438 (c) The Touch of Your Lips (Box 43, Folder 438)
  - Medley-439 (Box 43, Folder 439)
  - Medley-439 (a) A Little Bit (Box 43, Folder 439)
  - Medley-439 (b) Little White Lies (Box 43, Folder 439)
  - Medley-439 (c) Makin' Whoopee (Box 43, Folder 439)
  - Medley-440 (Box 43, Folder 440)
  - Medley-440 (a) Oh What It Seemed to Be (Box 43, Folder 440)
  - Medley-440 (b) My Devotion (Box 43, Folder 440)
  - Medley-440 (c) East of the Sea (Box 43, Folder 440)
  - Medley-441 (Box 43, Folder 441)
  - Medley-441 (a) This Heart of Mine (Box 43, Folder 441)
  - Medley-441 (b) Misty (Box 43, Folder 441)
  - Medley-441 (c) You'll Never Know (Box 43, Folder 441)
  - Medley-442 (Sammy Kay) (Box 43, Folder 442)
  - Medley-442 (a) Hawaiian Sunset (Box 43, Folder 442)
  - Medley-442 (b) Far Away Look in Your Eye (Box 43, Folder 442)
  - Medley-442 (c) Honestly (Box 43, Folder 442)
  - Medley-452 (Box 43, Folder 452)
  - Medley-452 (a) Whispering (Box 43, Folder 452)
  - Medley-452 (b) Blue (Box 43, Folder 452)
  - Medley-452 (c) Margie (Box 43, Folder 452)
  - Medley-458 (Box 43, Folder 458)
  - Medley-458 (a) Pretty Baby (Box 43, Folder 458)
  - Medley-458 (b) Couldn't Say Goodbye (Box 43, Folder 458)
  - Medley-458 (c) Elmer's Tune (Box 43, Folder 458)
  - Medley-459 (Box 43, Folder 459)
  - Medley-459 (a) Don't Take Your Love Away From Me (Box 43, Folder 459)
  - Medley-459 (b) Pretty Baby (Box 43, Folder 459)
  - Medley-460 (Box 43, Folder 460)
  - Medley-460 (a) Fascination (Box 43, Folder 460)
  - Medley-460 (b) Around the World (Box 43, Folder 460)
  - Medley-460 (c) Moon River (Box 43, Folder 460)
  - Medley-627 (Box 44, Folder 627)
  - Medley-627 (a) Does Your Heart Beat for Me (Box 44, Folder 627)
  - Medley-627 (b) Lonesome Old Road (Box 44, Folder 627)
  - Medley-627 (c) Careless (Box 44, Folder 627)
  - Medley-627 (d) Thinking of You (Box 44, Folder 627)
  - Misirlou (Box 42, Folder 332)
  - Misty (Box 43, Folder 429a)
  - Misty Blue (Box 40, Folder 134)
  - Misty Blue (Box 43, Folder 391)
  - Mood for Love Medley (Box 44, Folder 624)
  - Mood Indigo (Box 40, Folder 114)
  - Moon River (Box 42, Folder 323)
  - More (Box 43, Folder 412)
  - Most Beautiful Girl in the World (Box 42, Folder 327)
  - My Kind of Girl, Vocal (F) (Box 44, Folder 611)
  - My Prayer (Box 41, Folder 111)
  - My Prayer (Box 43, Folder 402)
  - My Prayer, Vocal (C) (Box 44, Folder 617)
  - My Silent Love (Box 40, Folder 154a)
  - My Way (Box 41, Folder 181)
  - Nancy, Vocal (Eb) (Box 44, Folder 607)
  - Nearness of You (Box 43, Folder 368)
  - Next 100 Years (Box 43, Folder 357)
  - New York, New York (Box 42, Folder 329)
  - Nice and Easy (Box 44, Folder 451)
  - Night Train (Box 41, Folder 204)
  - Object of My Affection (Box 43, Folder 375)
  - Oh You Beautiful Doll (Box 43, Folder 358)
  - Old Fashioned Way (Box 41, Folder 190)
  - Old Fashioned Way (Box 42, Folder 317)
  - Old Fashioned Way, Vocal (G) (Box 44, Folder 604)
  - On a Clear Day (Box 40, Folder 145)
  - One o'Clock Jump (Box 41, Folder 208)
  - Opus No. 1 (Box 41, Folder 254a)
  - Our Love Affair (Box 40, Folder 152)
  - Our Love is Here to Stay (Box 40, Folder 142)
  - Paper Moon (Box 42, Folder 335)
  - Patricia (Box 43, Folder 423)
  - Pennsylvania 6-5000 (Box 41, Folder 112)
  - Perdido (Box 43, Folder 372)
  - Phoenix (Box 41, Folder 199)
  - Please Release Me (Box 40, Folder 160)
  - Poor Butler Fly (Box 40, Folder 122)
  - Porte Alegre (Box 43, Folder 418)
  - Pra Que Discutir com Madame (Box 43, Folder 420)
  - Proud Mary (Box 41, Folder 191)
  - Quando, Quando (Box 42, Folder 348a)